Michael **Thullner**

Information Technology

(973) 356-7684 thullnerm@gmail.com

Toms River, NJ, 08753



linkedin.com/in/michaelthullner in

A graduate of Kean University with a BA in Communication Studies. Proven ability to build relationships through years of experience in the retail and sales industries. Quick learner with strong communication skills searching for new opportunities in which I can grow and be challenged in the IT industry.

SKILLS

- Active Directory/Azure Active Directory Experience
- Proficient with Adobe Products
- Proficient with Microsoft Office365 Products
- Powershell

- Experience managing Sharepoint sites
- Proficiency with Windows, iOS, Android
- Strong Verbal/Written Communication
- Strong Research/Multitasking ability

EDUCATION

Kean University Bachelor of Arts in Communication Union, NJ May 2020

3.6 GPA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Digacore Technology Consultants - NJ

March 2023 - Present

- L1 Help Desk Technician July 2023 Present
- Manage desktops, laptops, mobile devices, and IT infrastructure for 100+ clients across the United States.
- Monitor and administrate client networks using the Unifi portal and Sonicwall interface; including immediate/urgent support for Network outages and fluctuations and adopting/configuring networking hardware such as modems, routers, and switches.
- Create and manage multiple AD OUs, Security Groups, and Users for a large majority of clients.
- Create new tickets when needed and ensure tickets are properly documented from start to resolution.
- Utilize knowledge to assist other techs with specific issues/clients.
- Respond to client spam/security risks with urgency including blocking access to at risk users, utilizing message trace and content search to identify and purge threats, and reach out to necessary management or users to inform them about the potential risks and re-establish secure access.
- Ensure client DNS records, SSL certificates, and Licensing are up to date and configured properly.
- Work with various outside vendors ranging from Phone/Fax to ISPs to troubleshoot client issues.
- Configure and troubleshoot issues with tools/software such as 3CX, Acronis, Active Directory, Automate, Azure, Azure Virtual Desktop, Conditional Access, DNSfilter, Evident, Hyperspin, Intune, Multi-factor Authentication, Nerdio, Printix, Quick Assist, Remote Desktop Protocol, ScreenConnect.

Fast Team Technician – March 2023 – July 2023

- Received tickets via ConnectWise Manage ticketing system and utilized and ConnectWise Automate to assist in resolving end user issues.
- Multitasked by assisting users via ticketing system, phone queue, and live chat and ensured user satisfaction in a timely manner.
- Maintained, created, and updated documentation using IT Glue.
- Performed troubleshooting on issues relating, but not limited, to printers/fax/phone, network speed, user administration, hardware issues, software troubleshooting.
- Completed 72 tickets in a single day, breaking the previous company record of 54.

• Performed onsite service for clients where applicable including basic hands-on troubleshooting, upgrading server RAM, setting up additional displays, running cables, and cable management.

First Financial Federal Credit Union - NJ

February 2022 – Present

IT Help Desk Representative

- Received and resolved user issues through help desk ticketing system, document the troubleshooting process
- Built user workstations including System Unit, Multiple monitors, Peripherals, VOIP Phone, and UPS
- Managed and opened tickets/service calls with vendors to troubleshoot issues with network, database, security cameras, ATMs, etc.
- Utilized tools/software such as Exchange Admin Center, Sophos Central, DSUI, RDC, Dameware Mini Remote Control, PowerTerm, Active Directory Users & Computers, ManageEngine to complete daily tasks and troubleshooting
- Diagrammed alternative wiring method to better organize cables for our on-site server rack
- Installed new Samsung TV units in branches for advertisement display, including running display and data cables through walls/drop ceilings in accordance with fire code
- Experience crimping Category 5 cable to replace/install data cables in server racks
- Learned/used mySQL to troubleshoot an ongoing 'First Rewards' member rewards program tier issue.

AT&T | The Wireless Experience - NJ

September 2020 – November 2021

Sales Representative – September 2020 – November 2021

- Top sales rep in NJ in Nov 2021 with \$30,000.00+ gross profit
- Troubleshooted technical issues for guests' iOS and Android devices
- Researched sales leads and performed cold calls to offer products/services to guests

Store Manager – June 2021 – August 2021

- Developed and maintained strong customer relations to build upon sales leads
- Resolved any conflicts/issues at the store to ensure guest satisfaction
- Handled onboarding of new employees at store location

Shoprite Supermarkets - NJ

August 2016 - November 2020

Customer Service Representative/Bookkeeper

- Managed/Ordered tobacco inventory and succeeded in being top store in the company in tobacco sales.
- Established strong professional relationships with customers built upon a customer first mindset.
- Trained new cashiers and customer service representatives.
- Filled roles in multiple departments on a day-to-day basis based on staffing and need.
- Multiple time Employee of the Month
- Followed standard operating procedure in handling and ordering large amounts of currency.

PROFESSIONAL REFERENCES

Julio Pacheco – Manager AT&T | The Wireless Experience 732.575.8185

Daniel Malebranche – Coworker First Financial Federal Credit Union 908.415.7992

Yuri Gerson – Coworker Digacore Technology Consultants 908.692.2281